<!DOCTYPE idea-plugin PUBLIC "Plugin/DTD" "http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin.dtd">

<idea-plugin url="http://www.intellij.org/twiki/bin/view/Main/TabSwitchPlugin">
  <name>TabSwitch</name>
  <version>2.0</version>
  <idea-version since-build="8000" until-build="9499"/>
  <description><![CDATA[
    Open files/tabs switcher: allows to quickly switch between tabs with less keystrokes than
    Recent Files. Open files are selected from a list in most recently used order. This works
    very much like Alt-Tab in Windows or Ctrl-Tab in Opera. By default the action is mapped to
    Alt-A, but another popular assignment is Ctrl-Tab.<br><br>

    This plugin was initialy developed by Timur Zambalayev but I started fixing some bugs caused
    by openapi changes around April 2004. Since then I (Bas Leijdekkers) have taken over
    development.]]>
  </description>
  <change-notes>
    <![CDATA[
        2.0:<br> Completely reimplemented by Martin Fuhrer, with some additions by me. Now has the look
        of the Recent Files popup and better behavior in the presence of deleted files. Special thanks
        to Martin Fuhrer and Mark Scott.<br><br>

        1.7.1:<br> Fix for Selena does not use Recent Files limit when Tab Limit is 1, reported
        by Nathan Brown.<br><br> 

        1.7:<br> Changes for compatibility with Selena. Integrated Etienne Studer's
        PluginErrorReportSubmitter so that exceptions (should they happen) can be easily
        submitted.<br><br>

        1.6.1:<br> Previous version by accident only compiled for jdk 6.<br><br>

        1.6:<br> Fixed DialogWrapper.dispose() being called twice, causing a NullPointerException on
        IntelliJ IDEA build #5734.<br>
        Added scroll bar when many (default > 20) files are open. A big thank you to Krishna Raj,
        who provided this change.<br><br>

        1.5.1: Fixed java.lang.NoSuchMethodError in IDEA 5.0<br><br>

        1.5:<br>
        Fixed NullPointerException when no project open.<br>
        Added native IDEA look to popup window (thanks to Alexey Efimov).<br>
        Now uses same icons as on the editor tabs.<br>
        Added option to always show recent files even if tab limit is greater than 1<br>
        The plugin now uses Java 5 features and is retroweaved to work on jdk 1.4.2 and below.<br><br>

        1.0:<br>
        Worked around bug in IDEA 5.0.2 (FileEditorManagerListener.fileClosed() never called)<br>
        Used Recent Files Limit setting for those who have a Tab Limit settings of 1<br>
        Now possible to assign a key to quickly switch between two tabs without modifiers or
        pop-up window (thanks to Marc Juul Christoffersen)<br><br>

        0.7.5: Fixed NullPointerException introduced in previous version when opening new project
         in same frame.<br><br>

        0.7.4: All files opened when opening a project are now added to the TabSwitch menu again (bugfix
        for IDEA #3354)<br><br>
    ]]>
  </change-notes>
  <vendor email="leijdekkers@carp-technologies*NOSPAM*.nl">Bas Leijdekkers</vendor>
  <application-components>
    <component>
      <implementation-class>org.intellij.ideaplugins.tabswitch.TabSwitchSettings</implementation-class>
    </component>
  </application-components>
  <actions>
    <action
    id="TabSwitchPlugin.NextTab"
    class="org.intellij.ideaplugins.tabswitch.NextTabAction"
    text="Switch To Next Tab...">
      <keyboard-shortcut first-keystroke="alt A" keymap="$default"/>
    </action>
    <action
    id="TabSwitchPlugin.PreviousTab"
    class="org.intellij.ideaplugins.tabswitch.PreviousTabAction"
    text="Switch To Previous Tab...">
      <keyboard-shortcut first-keystroke="shift alt A" keymap="$default"/>
    </action>
  </actions>
  
  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <errorHandler implementation="nu.studer.idea.errorreporting.PluginErrorReportSubmitter"/>
  </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
