<!DOCTYPE idea-plugin PUBLIC "Plugin/DTD" "http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin.dtd">

<idea-plugin url="https://github.com/mustah/TabSwitch">
  <name>TabSwitch3</name>
  <version>3.0.7</version>
  <idea-version since-build="135.690"/>

  <description><![CDATA[
    Open files/tabs switcher to quickly switch between tabs with less keystrokes than
    Recent Files. Open files are selected from a list in most recently used order, similarly
    to Alt+Tab in Windows or Ctrl-Tab in Opera. By default the action is mapped to
    Alt+A, but another popular assignment is CMD+E.<br><br>

    Thanks to Timur Zambalayev for the original plugin, Martin Fuhrer for a major contribution
    in the form of a rewrite and Mark Scott for patching a bug. Follow further development of
    <a href="https://github.com/mustah/TabSwitch">this plugin on GitHub</a> or follow
    <a href="https://twitter.com/_musten_">me on twitter</a> for announcements and other things.<br/><br/>
    ]]>
  </description>
  <change-notes><![CDATA[
    3.0.7: Bug-fix: reverse recent files array _before_ checking their validity do be added to list.<br/>
    3.0.6: Remove TabSwitch settings. Is not used anymore.<br/>
    3.0.5: Project is upgraded to use java 7.<br/>
    3.0.4: When only one file is opened - do not display the TabSwitch list. Also some refactorings.<br/>
    3.0.3: Lots of code clean ups. Does not display same file in the list twice anymore.<br/>
    3.0.2: Do not include directories when listing recent VCS changes popup window. Removed light green background color from popup list.<br/>
    3.0.1: Added new TabSwitch Action to display modified files in the default change list of your VCS. Large refactoring.<br>
    3.0.0: Fixed bug where it moved two steps down on each move-down-action.<br/>
    2.2.0: Cleaning up some code.<br>
    2.1.9: Switch to open tab even if it is located in a different split pane.<br>
    2.1.8: The TabSwitch actions are now available during background indexing in Maia.<br>
    2.1.7: Fix for mouse over popup changes selection problem reported by Michael Bushe.<br>
    2.1.6: RubyMine compatible version.<br><br/>
  ]]></change-notes>

  <vendor url="https://twitter.com/_musten_" email="must.tahir@gmail.com">Must</vendor>

  <project-components>
    <component>
      <implementation-class>org.intellij.ideaplugins.tabswitch.TabSwitchProjectComponent</implementation-class>
    </component>
  </project-components>

  <actions>
    <action
      id="org.intellij.ideaplugins.tabswitch.action.NextTabAction"
      class="org.intellij.ideaplugins.tabswitch.action.NextTabAction"
      text="Next tab">
    </action>
    <action
      id="TabSwitchPlugin.NextVcsChangeAction"
      class="org.intellij.ideaplugins.tabswitch.action.NextVcsChangeAction"
      text="Next VCS change tab">
    </action>
    <action
      id="TabSwitchPlugin.SwitchTab"
      class="org.intellij.ideaplugins.tabswitch.action.SwitchTabAction"
      text="Switch Between Two Tabs (No UI, No Keyboard Modifier Needed)">
    </action>
  </actions>

  <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>
</idea-plugin>
